instantsalespages.com 2016-01-30

# Privacy Policy | www.instantsalespages.com

Privacy Statement  
instantsalespages.com site visit its website every respect the privacy of individuals. We collect any of your information will be used to meet the requirements of any service you may provide you with information on new products and new services, and to improve the level of service we have for you. Your data will be handled in accordance with the provisions of EU and national laws and regulations. Your information will not be disclosed to any person other than instantsalespages.com website, its subsidiaries and distributors.

We will use your personal information:  
We will use your personal data to:  
1> according to your privacy settings, have been released by the open information you  
2> Depending on your settings, allowing you to properly use this site  
3> perform general customer management  
4> send to you on our website, as well as other products and services  
5> according to your personal information to provide you with the appropriate ad  
6> investigation of fraud and violations of our Terms of Use

Cookie Usage  
cookies are small amounts of data, in case you did not refuse to accept cookies in, cookies will be sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to store your data access our site, when you access or visit our website again, we can identify you, and by analyzing more data to provide better service for you. You have the option to accept or reject cookies. You can modify your browser settings to refuse to accept cookies, but we need to remind you, because you refuse to accept cookies, you may not rely on cookies to use some features of our site.

What personal information will be collected  
We collect your personal information through the registry form. This information may include your name, email address, country and language preferences and other data. We use this information for:  
1\. to make your visit more enjoyable experience  
2\. to send you relevant information about products and services  
3\. from time to time send you e-mail us think about promotions, products and services you may be interested in If you would like to receive information or identity of our other communication modes of transmission, you can tick the relevant box to select in the registry. If you do not wish to receive any communication and dissemination of information from us, you can always inform us by email. If you allow us to use for the above purposes your personal information, we may from time to entrust our behalf handle e-mail or other means of direct marketing communication company or organization to disclose such information. If true, we guarantee you the information to deal with any third-party companies will comply with the relevant data protection legislation.

The way we share information  
Without your consent, we will not be visiting the personal information of persons, share, or sell to any business use, this information can only be used to provide instantsalespages.com website and your brand message. However, integration and statistical data of persons who visit our site can be shared with our partners and sometimes, we will keep your personal information (such as: name, mailing address, e-mail address) with instantsalespages.com agent website , contractor or partner share, its scope is limited to services such individuals or entities instantsalespages.com site offers together with the provision of services or instantsalespages.com website. In addition to providing services to instantsalespages.com sites, such persons can not be other ways to share this information can not be used or re-sell this data. For example: We can provide the agent, contractor or partner of your personal information, for data processing services, used to notify contest winners, so they can send you to request product samples or provide your information.

Information collected  
This website collects personal information in other circumstances you voluntarily provide information. We may here will collect your personal information or information obtained from third parties to integrate, to provide you with better customer service. This website uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience to understand your use of the Site Services habits, to improve our quality of service. When you visit our website or use some of our products, the site's servers automatically record information, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of use. When you visit our site, we will be advertising through third-party advertising companies. These companies may use information about your visit to this site and other sites situation (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) in order to show you that you may be interested in advertising products and services.

Security  
Please note that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. To prevent the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction, we will take reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information through a computer to transfer the site. In particular, the transmission to the Site or the Site's e-mail sent from the possible unsafe, so pay special attention to determine what information you send via e-mail. In addition, when you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special login feature on this site, please ensure the security of such information.
